Esenbike..
You see the situation Ulugan is in.
His fate...
...is not just the price of what he has done.
It is also...
...a lesson for those...
...who walk on the same path with him.
Osman!
Do you think there won't be a
price for this insolence and insult?
Alps!
Mother..
They have more men than we do.
So you are saying you planned
your trap long ago, Osman, huh?
When I die here like a hero...
...your fate... -Shut up
Shut up!
May your word be as short as your life!
Like a flooding river...
...the furor that will rain on the frontiers...
...will drown you with its anger.
Sea, huh?
Sea?
I will shed your dirty blood...
...and I will stain the sea with that blood.
I will make endless mountains
out of your severed heads.
You will see what nursing a grudge...
..costs here.
All of you!
My Bey!
Protect Osman Bey!
I am here, Ulugan!
Where do you think you are running? Where?
Shields! -Move!
Clear!
Move!
Alps! Attack!
Walk nokers! Come on!
Alps!
Turn this place into hell for them!
Come on!
Come on, open the door!
Bala.
You need me.
You will never be able to find Halime.
Hold the exits.
Soldiers!
Attack!
My Shahzade, the door is open!
Next time...
Soldiers!
Take the Priestess!
Mother... The door is open! Come on!
-Come on! Come on!
-Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Damn it!
Here... Get in.
Wait... Wait... -Come.
I have it.
Are you alright?
Leave me here.
I will slow you down.
Go, Bala Hatun.
You are the key that will
take me to my daughter.
We will not leave you here.
You kept coming to the frontiers!
Which one of you escaped the
Turks' swords, huh? Which one?
Ulugan!
Esenbike!
You will die soon.
You, whose state I have crushed under my feet...
...think I am powerless huh?
Ulugan! I am here Ulugan! Get up!
You will recover! Come on! Come.
Come! You will recover for our revenge! Come on!
Come on nokers!
Attack!
My Bey! Ulugan is running away!
Boran!
Cerkutay!
Go after them!
As you order, my Bey!
Brother..
We need to kill these first.
Come on!
Come on.
Mother, we are losing our nokers one by one.
We must not be overwhelmed by
our ambition and die in Osman's trap.
The battle has just begun, Osman.
We'll meet again.
Nokers will stay behind us and protect us.
We are leaving.
Come on.
Alps! Beys!
First, we will crush the
snake's tail, then its head.
Open the door!
Mother! This door cannot hold much longer.
We need to leave this place now! Come on!
Come on! Hurry up! This way
Come on! -Leave now!
Come on! Leave!
Come on
Come on, come on.
-Hurry!
-Help!
They've broken the door and are coming.
Gulce, give me the flying flame.
Light... The door.. This
way! We have to go this way.
Alaaddin.
-You go!
-Mother.
-Mother, come on.
Hold on.
Come to me.
Come to me, you dogs.
O Allah.
Soldiers, stop
Esenbike must have left watchmen behind.
Kanyumaz!
-My Bey.
-Follow them.
-As you order, my Bey.
Won't we go after them, my Bey?
-No.
She must have got out of the forest by now.
We can't catch even if we
My Bey.
My Bey, Ulugan has escaped.
They left the carriage somewhere in the woods.
And they moved on foot.
We couldn't trace.
Altuga is as good at hiding
the traces as I'm good at tracing.
I opened such a sword wound in his chest...
...he can't go far away.
He'll come out sooner or later.
We're going to our tribe.
We'll have a council and set the target.
Beys.
You are coming with us.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Mother.
-Yes?
We got one step closer to Halime.
Thanks to Allah. We found
out my daughter's name.
We'll find more, mother.
You'll be together soon.
God willing.
Kismet, prepare the disguises.
Sofia will come after us. We should
give Osman Bey the great news.
Alaaddin, let's go!
That woman has to die before she speaks, Hristo.
She told Bala Poena's name.
If we can't catch them,
she will tell her everything.
Let's go faster.
We have to find them
before they arrive in the tribe.
Let's go!
I told you. Osman is like no other enemies.
He plans every detail.
It seems you admire Osman a lot.
You should know I'm like
no other enemies either.
Many like Osman died under my feet.
I'm only praying for Allah
to take Osman's life tonight.
I have no other thoughts.
That's what is going to happen, Begum Hatun.
Osman is going to pass away tonight
at his most defenseless moment.
Osman isn't going to carry a sword tonight.
Tonight is the best time to kill him.
He should thank us. We're
going to kill him at Qadr night.
Tell alps to provide tighter
security around the tribe.
Sure, my Bey.
Host the Beys until the council
starts. Tell Sahin Bey to come.
-As you order, my Bey.
This way, Beys.
This way, please.
Welcome, father.
-Where is your mother, my dear?
-We were waiting for them.
I hope they aren't in trouble, father.
What if that demon tricked them?
No, my dear. We know about all their tricks.
Maybe, they are coming back with good news, huh?
-God willing.
-God willing, God willing.
Poena!
Bala!
What's going on, Bala?
They named our daughter Poena, my Bey.
What?
-How? Where is she?
-We'll know everything, my Bey.
Take her to the healing tent!
Cauterize her wound carefully, sisters!
Lucia.
-Who is she? -Priestess Lucia.
Just as she was about to speak,
Sofia arrived and tried to kill her.
Sofia... Demon
Although she's trying to keep our daughter
away, she's bringing her closer to us!
Don't worry. Very soon.
-Very soon.
-Yes.
-My Hatun.
-My Bey.
Are you going to battles
even though you are pregnant?
If you don't take me with you, I go with mother.
Besides, my baby is pleased with this.
Well... He's like his father, huh?
-Yes.
-Of course, yes.
Come on, let's go.
Tengri (Turkish-Mongolian God)
will heal you, Ulugan.
Your soul will be purified from the death.
You'll repel the dark spirits...
...and heal Ulugan, Shaman.
Otherwise, I won't let you live.
His armor saved his life. He's going to recover.
Yet..
...dark spirits want him, Altuga.
Then repel those spirits, Shaman.
Ulugan! Ulugan! Ulugan!
Ulugan is reborn every day!
Wake up for vengenace, Ulugan!
She's the priestess who looked
after our daughter for years, huh?
She's the witness of
the years they stole from us.
She knows everything
we want to know, my Bey.
Alaaddin, help her recover somehow, son.
I'll do my best, father.
We'll help her live, with Allah's will.
-God willing. God willing.
-God willing.
Is your daughter's name Poena?
The priestess was going
to tell us everything, but...
But the snake Sofia didn't let her.
What's that supposed to mean?
Lucia, why did you do such a thing?
Why did you give my name?
Her name isn't Poena but Halime.
They made my sister
forget us and everything else.
Whatever they did to her mind,
...she has our soul and our blood.
They can never change her.
Don't be worrying.
Right.
When we come back together, we
will help her remember everything.
Tell Ulgen to prepare sherbet.
She needs to regain strength.
Bala, let's go.
-Son.
My Bey.
Let's go, Bala.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
-Alaaddin Bey.
-Yes?
How can a person even forget?
They said..
Halime can't remember.
Those who want to do evil things
may find many ways, Meryem.
Is it possible to forget everything?
It's possible.
Of course, it is. I once heard in the madrasah.
But I've never seen it.
They play with the mind, Meryem.
There are many poisons in the nature.
But not all of them kill.
They make you lose your mind.
Did you drink the syrup?
No, it got broken before I could drink.
Damn it, Poena.
Here. Don't forget to take.
Keep it carefully.
The syrup bottles.
Yes.
You're right, Meryem.
Praise be, you're very smart.
I couldn't think of that.
Let me go check them.
Am I...
Am I Halime?
Aykut Cavus, tell the dervishes...
...to be my guests at Qadr night.
As you order, my Bey.
-You tell Beys to come to my tent.
-As you order, my Bey.
Mother Sultan, I insist.
We should wait no longer.
We should slaughter Osman's people tonight.
-He already deserved this.
-That would be great.
If we slaughter people now.
...not only Kayi people but also all the
Muslims in the frontiers will rise against us.
We have enough power to make them all kneel.
What are we waiting for? Will
we let Osman get stronger?
Never.
The day after tomorrow
...even Osman's name will
be wiped out of these lands.
I will do such thing...
-Do I have permission?
-Come in, Altuga.
I've brought Ulugan. He's in the healing tent.
Shaman says he's recovering fast.
Good.
That means we will do away with Osman together.
The traps set against Turks...
Those who do their best to separate us...
You know how treacherous...
...how sinister...
...they are.
You showed us the evil disguised
as goodness, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
This foresight will bring Kayi back
to its old days, Allah knows the best.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
The punches we have
thrown at the infidels so far...
...have surprised them greatly.
...only one final punch...
...remains.
My Bey, give us the order and we will kill them.
No, not while our hands are in the air.
They will understand when
the punch pierces their chest.
Until then, we will make our moves secretly.
The last move before
we rise against the infidels.
Our troops and the Alps of the Turkmen Beys...
...will unite in the quarters.
Together...
...we will become one army.
Each of our tribes is in a
different place around the frontier.
Gathering our troops in the quarters without
the Mongols noticing will be very difficult.
Of course, freedom is not
something easily gained.
Of course, it will be difficult.
If the issue is the Turk's
struggle for freedom...
...the Beys will do their duty
without any mistakes, my Bey.
You just order us, my Bey.
Death on this path is the
most honorable fate for us.
Orhan, tell your bravest Alps to set out.
The Sivrioyuk location, which is
far from us but close to the infidels.
We will set up our secret quarters there.
As you order my Bey.
While we unite in the quarters...
...we will become one army.
Then, we will take back our tribe.
-God willing, my Bey.
-God willing.
Sargun!
Your anger towards Osman
even burns the ground you step on.
But a chained anger is useless.
I will strangle you..
...with that chain, Ilbay.
What do you want?
Osman's lost hopes..
...rise again with faith.
Esenbike is making a mistake.
Now is the time to attack and destroy their joy.
Osman.
Osman will drown in his own blood tonight.
What about Esenbike?
War has no faith, Ilbay.
If necessary, I will get the
allegiance of my enemies with blood.
But I will not let them feel joy.
Sargun.
Let me come with you.
I know Osman well.
I know.
You are talented in letting Osman escape.
But..
But you can be of use to me there.
Get ready.
Ilbay.
What is he going to do?
We will kill Osman tonight.
They have removed all the traces.
That doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
I already know their secret little tribe.
Are we going to raid their tribe?
No.
Osman must have already taken every precaution.
I will go...
...and take care of this
matter myself, in silence.
This is very dangerous.
Not as dangerous as
letting that fool live, Hristo.
I will kill her tonight.
Let's go.
I seek refuge with Allah from Satan, the accursed
In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate.
We sent it down on the Night of Glory.
What will explain to you what that Night of Glory is?
The Night of Glory is better than a thousand months;
on that night the angels and the Spirit descend...
again and again with their
Lord’s permission on every task;
[there is] peace that night until the break of dawn.
Allah the Almighty said the truth.
Surah Al-Qadr [1-5]
Peace be upon the messengers
and praise be to God the Lord of all the Worlds.
-Surah As-Saffat [181-182]-
Al Fatiha
May Allah's blessings and greetings
be upon Hadrath Muhammed, peace be upon him.
Osman Bey Secret Tents
Come on, let's sit down.
Let's drink some sherbet, huh?
Drink, Osman, drink.
This will be the last thing you drink.
Attack!
Follow them.
They ran away again, my Bey.
How did this happen, my Bey?
The infidels united again.
Clearly, it's Sofia's plan. She helped them.
Sofia, Sofia, Sofia. Sofia
is behind everything again.
You were right, my Bey. We
did well by evacuating the tribe.
But how did you know these
dogs would attack, my Bey?
They have no faith.
I knew they would attack
at our most sacred moment.
However...
...their hopes got stuck
in their throats, my Bey.
We will slit that throat soon.
Come on, we are going to
Sogut. This fear is enough for them.
On this blessed night, which is better than
a thousand months, your breath healed us.
Thank you.
Don't even mention it.
You hosted us.
We were honored to perform our dhikr in Sogut...
...where Sheikh Edebali's
breath touched, Alaeddin Bey.
May Allah be pleased with you.
Thank you.
May Allah grant my Osman Bey and his
descendants many victories, God willing.
Aameen.
Thank you.
May Allah keep your dhikr and breath lasting
in the whole world, God willing, dear Dervish.
Thank you. Then we should
ask for your permission to leave.
Don't even ask.
It was a pleasure to meet.
May Allah protect you.
Mother...
Yes my daughter.
I want to ask you something, but...
I am a bit ashamed..
...because I don't know...
Ask me, my daughter. Don't feel
ashamed because you do not know.
I've heard it many times from you actually.
I am surprised that I never
wondered about it before.
Will you say it, my daughter?
There is no God but Allah.
As if it holds all the
beauty of the world in it.
What is in these words that mesmerizes
Dervishes, you and other Muslims?
Mother, what does it mean?
There is no God (in Arabic)
There is no God (in Turkish)
But Allah (in Arabic)
But Allah (in Turkish)
He is above everything. He is the
Ruler of everything, and the only Creator.
That is the meaning my daughter.
You called it mesmerizing...
That word does not mesmerize us.
It is realizing our weakness
before Allah's Greatness.
It is love.
This is what dhikr does to us.
It seems it has touched you too, my daughter.
But you will find out
what it means for yourself.
Come on.
What happened?
Where have you been, Sargun?
He did not listen to you
and went to attack Osman.
If I had not been there
...they would have fallen into Osman's trap.
A Hanzade does not need your help.
The blood of the Great
Genghis flows in his veins.
If you are from Genghis's lineage, I am
from the lineage of the Great Roman Emperor.
Do not be above yourself.
Those who are above
themselves become Osman's prey.
Just like Commander Ulugan.
Tell me.
Where is he now?
Hatun!
Watch your words.
Or you will become a prisoner of your words!
Soldiers!
Go ahead and kill each other.
Esenbike.
I did not come here to be enemies
I came here to work with you.
Because we both have a common enemy.
Osman.
Soldiers!
Get out!
I and Esenbike Hatun...
...have things to talk about.
Everyone leave!
So, you went to Osman's tribe to kill him.
Do you have that much power?
To defeat Osman, you need more than just power.
You need wisdom.
Because there is a wolf standing against us.
A sneaky and smart wolf.
I turn wolves into fur to wear on my back.
While you were wasting
time in Osman's empty tribe...
...I was planning incredible games here.
What kind of a game?
A game that will become a disaster for Osman.
And you will help me against our common enemy.
It was wonderful.
The dhikr of dervishes
purified our hearts, my Osman.
The whole Sogut enjoyed it.
Praise be. Praise be.
But I was thinking about you.
I'm worried about the tribe.
We laid a trap for heathens
but they survived, Bala.
How is the priestess doing? Did she wake up?
We're waiting for the medicine to take effect.
Bala... We'll find our
daughter. You know that, right?
I know.
We'll get our child back.
I know this just like I know
we will take our tribe back.
We will take it back.
The reinforcements of the beys are on the
way. I'll welcome them with the alps tomorrow.
We'll take them to the new headquarters.
Praise be. We've lost too many recently.
Our army will get stronger with this.
Yes, don't worry. I'll be cautious all the time.
Gather people with Alaaddin and you
two take them to the new headquarters.
Yes. I'll finish the
preparations quickly, Osman.
We can't stay here any longer, anyway.
No.
No matter what, in case of any hardships
...you stand strong even
without souring your face.
And? Then what?
Well... I fall in love again.
In this world,
...you are my source of gratitude.
You are my source of gratitude, my Osman.
Osman the Brunette.
Your eyes are my hopes.
You'll make thing even better than before.
I will.
Don't worry. I will.
I will make things right again.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
The position of the troop to
come is behind that mountain.
We're getting close, but...
...God willing, our alps will arrive
safe and sound too, Osman Bey.
Do you have a problem, Guralp Bey?
Tell us, Guralp Bey. Why are you concerned?
Do you know anything?
I know..
...Esenbike whose tricked got exposed...
...may do any kind of evil things now.
I know why you are concerned.
Esenbike may have realized
that our armies would get united.
But don't worry.
If they use the route we give them
...Mongolians will never notice them.
Come on. Let's go take our warriors.
Alaaddin.
When will this medicine take effect, son?
Shall we give her other medicine?
No, mother. I did everything
that should be done.
We will just wait.
Mother, don't worry.
Obviously, she's a weak one.
That's why it takes effect late.
-She'll open her eyes soon, God willing.
-God willing, Alaaddin Ali.
God willing.
There is a marshland ahead.
Riding the horses may be dangerous.
We'll go on foot.
My Bey.
This silence bothers you too, right?
Even jackals and birds
are making no noise. Well...
You're right.
This place doesn't seem safe.
You're right about your doubts, Osman!
Esenbike.
Wolves, birds and all the
animals have been muted!
Waiting to watch your death!
Osman..
The great commander of Mongolians, Ulugan...
...who you tried to kill and whose
hatred you drew on yourself is here too.
You..
Yes, me.
I will take more from you..
...than the pain you left in my chest.
You will regret that I didn't cut you
into a thousand pieces, you vile dog.
We're surrounded, my Bey.
They're too many.
How did they know about our route, my Bey?
It seems their scouts noticed us.
Sahin Bey.
You got my message and came here quickly, huh?
I heard.
You were Osman's guest
for the sake of Qadr night.
Where is my son?
Show him to me now.
Your son is alive.
Don't worry.
He's been our guest.
We had some talk.
My son, are you alright?
He's fine. For now.
Don't do this, hatun.
I'll serve you. Don't.
You will.
You will be my servant for your son's life.
You'll tell me about Osman's every step.
What now, my Bey?
How will we survive this evil trap?
Kanyumaz.
Take some alps with you.
When we attack, run away before they notice.
Go and meet the Beys.
And take them to Catalkaya.
As you order, my Bey.
Did you become blind and deaf
when you saw our power, Osman?
For the shield wall.
Wait for my call.
-Okay, my Bey.
-What are we waiting for?
-Let's wash our swords with blood!
-Not now, Ulugan!
I want to give Osman a last chance.
What is it?
Let me know!
A chance to live, Osman.
You'll see.
Before you could reach the armies
you were expecting, you got trapped!
Now drop your sword and surrender.
...won't lose their lives.
Fools, huh?
The ones behind me are Turks!
Don't confuse them with your looters!
A wolf never walks not to die.
You may be stronger than us.
But you can never...
...wipe us out of people's hearts!
We may fall on the ground!
But our names, reputations
and our children following us...
...will always make people like you pay for it!
-Close.
-Alps, shield wall!
Archers, attack!
Nokers, shield wall!
Shield wall, nokers!
Open!
Close!
Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
-Go now. As you order, my Bey.
Open!
-Close!
-Open!
Open! Close!
Close! Open!
My Bey, arrows are raining over us.
Ambush! Alaaddin!
Alps, take position!
-Bala!
-Ulgen, take women and children into the woods.
You snake. You never die!
Bala!
This is the end.
Kill them all!
Attack!
It's time for the unfinished business, Bala.
I'll be your death, Begum.
Hide. Protect yourself.
If the priestess wakes up, she'll try
to harm you to take revenge from me.
Hide.
Protect the priestess!
You'll never be able to reach your target.
I have to kill you first then, huh?
That's not going to happen, Sofia.
Today, you are the ones to die!
Attack!
Close!
Open!
Hold on, warrior. Hold on.
Come on.
-Orhan, your turn.
-Alright.
Their resistance got broken,
Esenbike. We should attack.
There is still time. Keep shooting arrows!
Do they never run out of arrows?
When they do, you'll see what I'm going to do.
We're trapped here.
Are these shields enough to protect us?
My Bey, if we don't attack now
we may never get out of here.
No, just wait.
We have to hold on. Be patient.
I'm out of patience. Attack, nokers!
They're attacking, my Bey.
-We should leave the cover.
-We'll wait, Cerkutay.
We have to wait.
Draw your swords.
Open!
Osman...
...isn't going to give up, Esenbike Hatun.
Open!
My Bey!
-My Bey!
Are you alright, my Bey?
I'm fine, don't worry.
It's just a tiny wound!
You'll face the cold side of my sword shortly!
Your daring will bring your death, Ulugan!
Time is ticking for you!
Time is ticking for you.
Come on, warriors!
Your end has come, Begum
-I will not die before I kill you, Bala!
-Say the shahada!
Traitor!
Gonca.
You go to the cart, protect the
Priestess. We will handle this here.
How can I leave you alone, Holofira?
Gonca, come on, they are coming.
There are too many of them,
Holofira. Come on, let's go.
Ulgen, gather the people.
Mother. Mother, they are killing
the people, what will we do now?
We are retreating. To the
horses, to the cart, come on.
Do you think we will let you go, Alaeddin?
We will see. We will see.
Come on, to the horses.
They are escaping. Run.
Run!
Alps! Flying flames!
They escaped!
Bala!
Do not stop! Kill them with your swords!
Now!
My Bey, their nokers are too many.
We cannot fight them with a few men.
We had them place the nokers across the region.
Now we will lure them to us.
Come on, Alps!
Now!
You are running Osman, huh?
Now they will come after me.
Boran and I will go north.
Orhan, you will go south.
They will follow us.
After we get rid of them, you
will go to Catalkaya with the Beys.
Ulugan! Go after him! Catch Osman!
-Come on, to the horses.
-Come on, Beys.
Sargun, you go after Ulugan as well.
As you order, mother.
Alaeddin, how is the Priestess?
Did you check her, my son?
I did, mother. She is alright.
Good.
The fog has slowed them
down a lot. They cannot catch us.
We will continue through this
forest. They will not find us this way.
This way! Come on! -Come on!
My Bey, are you alright?
I am alright. I am.
My Bey, your wound has weakened
you. We need to cauterize it.
Esenbike revealed our plan.
Let's first get rid of those following us.
Then we need to determine
the route with the Beys.
My Bey, there is a cave ahead.
At least we can stop the
bleeding there. Then we can go.
Come on my Bey...
Let's hide the horses then.
Altuga... Find where they are.
Hurry, Altuga.
They cannot have gone too far with that wound.
They are somewhere around here.
Where are they, Altuga?
They went this way, Ulugan.
Osman Bey Headquarters
Alps, take the wounded to
the healing tents, come on.
Gonca, take the Priestess
to the tent, my daughter.
As you order, mother.
Alps, send out watchmen immediately.
Take positions around the quarters.
I do not want any weakness know that. Come on.
Slowly...
Those dogs will not hold
back. Sofia is after the Priestess.
Kismet, place the sisters
at the Priestess' door.
Bala Hatun.
That woman, Sofia... Why did
she want to kill the Priestess?
Isn't she her friend?
She is cruel enough to kill the woman
who has been her companion for years.
She does not love anyone. She
doesn't know what friendship is.
Mother...
You know, they attacked us...
What if they attack my father and Orhan?
May Allah forbid, my daughter.
God willing they are safe.
Nothing bad will happen.
You look a little pale. Take some rest.
Fatma, your aunt is entrusted to you.
-Do not worry, mother.
Come on.
Mother.
Lucia is not well.
She moved too much her wound opened.
Alaeddin, do your best
and help her survive, my son.
She will bring Halime to us.
If necessary, I will wait
next to her until she dies.
I will do my best, mother.
I need to talk to Lucia.
Come on, son, come on.
Come on.
Bala Hatun.
I can stay with Lucia. If she
wakes up, I will let you know.
You have a lot to do.
That would be very good, my daughter. Very good.
Then I entrust my daughter
and her secret to you, alright?
I promise. I will not even blink there.
Good.
Rider nokers...
Those dastards are replaced
by new ones the moment they die.
Let them come.
We will keep fighting until we kill them all.
Come on!
That's all!
No one else is coming.
Ulugan sent most of his nokers after Osman Bey.
God willing my Bey is alright.
With that wound...
...it will be difficult for him to escape.
Are we going to ask for a
support unit for Osman Bey?
No...
We will follow Osman Bey's orders.
Get ready.
We will wait for him at Catalkaya.
I cannot understand, my Bey...
I keep thinking...
But I cannot find its answer.
Esenbike..
How did she find out about our route?
Clearly...
Clearly, there is a traitor among us.
Who do you think it is, my Bey? Which dog?
He will show up in the end...
We will punish him when he shows up.
But now, what matter is to...
...get over this hardship as soon as
possible before we lose more men.
My Bey, Ulugan and his dogs are after us.
They are looking for you everywhere.
We will get out, but how?
That's better... Let him come after us.
While he is after us, we'll change our plan...
...and go to the tribe.
My Bey, we have not gathered our army yet.
Alright, we cauterized your wound.
But this wound will weaken you, my Bey.
How are we going to take the
tribe when we are in this state?
I will explain how when we meet with the Beys.
Now go to Bala..
Tell her what happened.
They will go to the tribe from the quarters.
As you order my Bey.
This cave is the only place we
haven't checked around here, Ulugan.
They are here.
Spread out!
Check everywhere!
They found us, my Bey.
Why did my aunt want to kill you?
Why did you say Halime's name was Poena?
Please, wake up.
Lucia..
Poena, is that you?
Thank God, you are alive.
Why did my aunt do this?
She loves you.
She cannot love anyone. Poena.
Are you alright?
I am confused.
My aunt said Halime was dead.
Why did you tell Bala my name?
Sofia.
Don't trust her.
You cannot trust her.
Bala.
What do you mean?
My aunt means.
...the world to me.
She is my only family.
Did you forget?
Bala killed..
...my mother!
May God forgive us.
Forgive me Poena.
Tell me Lucia.
Halime died, right?
My aunt is telling the truth...
Halime...
Halime is alive.
Now Osman...
...then Orhan will die.
As long as our spy Sahin is among them...
...every step they will take will be useless.
Osman..
You were afraid of becoming my
prey and took refuge in this cave, huh?
Right...
When jackals invade the wolf's tent...
...the wolf will surely revive in a cave.
I also wanted to finish what we started.
Now it is time.
Now...
You should forget about resurrection.
These are your final moments.
Is that so?
We'll see now.
Flying flame!
Come on!
My Bey.. Are you alright?
-I am.
My Bey, God willing we can
find a way out as you said.
We will.
There is a light over there.
I guess there's a way, let's go.
Okay my Bey..
Has Osman lost his mind?
He trapped himself inside to escape from us.
So just to turn this cave into our grave...
...you gave up on yourself too, Osman.
Osman wouldn't do this if
he hadn't planned a way out.
We will look for another way.
Come on. Start walking around.
Come on.
He won't expect us to get out from this place.
They must be after us.
Let's go to the horses.
And you will go to the quarters immediately.
Inform Bala Hatun.
Now they will set out...
...to the tribe from the quarters.
My Bey, as you order, but...
But what?
My Bey, your wound seems really deep.
I cannot leave you alone here.
Do not make me repeat my word!
If we need to die, we will die! Today,
our banner will be raised in our tribe!
As you order my Bey.
Hurry up! Look under every
stone! Check everywhere!
They are coming. Come on, to the horses!
Let's go!
They got out from here.
We'll go after them now.
Not we, Ulugan.
Altuga will.
You and I will go to my mother.
Apparently, this Osman won't stop.
We will ask her what to do.
So you are saying these are all the
Turkmen Beys that have come to Catalkaya.
Is that right, Kanyumaz?
There are this many people on their way as
well who have received our word my Shahzade.
With Allah's permission they will arrive soon.
Alright.
My Shahzade, Osman Bey is coming.
Clear the way.
Come here, you traitor...
Come here..
Show yourself!
Who are you talking to, Osman Bey?
The traitor among us knows who he is.
Show yourself!
My Bey..
Forgive me.
Forgiveness, huh?
Then... Kneel
How can you ask for forgiveness?
Forgive me, my Bey!
So
...you were the one who informed
Esenbike of our route, huh?
So you lured us into a trap.
So you were the reason of all
the lives we've lost, is that right?
Huh?
My Bey, how did you find that out?
How did I learn about this?
First Osman and then Orhan are going to die.
As long as our spy Sahin is among them
...we'll know about their every step.
They threatened me with my son's life, my Bey.
I made a mistake. Please.
Forgive me.
-Shut up!
Shut up!
I will never forgive you.
For your own son's life,
...you sacrificed many sons of the state, huh?
Huh? For yourself!
You sacrificed all those Beys
and alps who would die for freedom!
Look at me! Look!
No.
Even if I forgive you as a father,
...the state will never forgive this betrayal.
He's neither the first nor
the last traitor among us!
But traitors like him can never stop
the ones walking in the right path!
Definitely, my Bey.
This vile dog ruined the plan...
...that we created with great efforts.
Some more reinforcements units are on the way.
Mongolians know our intention now. How
can we gather them in the headquarters?
No.
We aren't going to the headquarters.
We're going somewhere else.
How could Bala run away with a
few Turkmen from all those nokers?
We lost their traces after the dense forest.
Yet we will definitely catch them, Esenbike.
If you let them win again, I
will choke you myself, Ilbay.
Osman has run away, Esenbike.
Nokers are tracing them.
What now?
If you leave the prey
wounded, he will be the predator.
Osman will continue his plan.
We'll kill him before he gathers the units.
Ilbay, go to the tribe quickly and
take measures in case of a riot.
We'll take out Osman's and his men's
hearts and make Mongolians prevail!
All those alps hit the road.
...crossed the border and reached
Kayi lands dealing with troubles.
But now you say the plan has changed, Osman Bey.
What's in your mind, Osman Bey?
Will we send our men back to our tribes?
The way back must be full of ambushes and traps.
That way will lead our men to death.
I said we won't go to the headquarters.
But I didn't say we will give up.
Our enemies will think we're going to
gather our armies in the headquarters.
They'll think we intend to do that.
Let them think so.
They will be looking for us everywhere.
But we will march towards Kayi
Tribe that they left unprotected.
Remember!
We have a tribe to save from the dark clouds...
..and a cause with whose light
will spread all around the world!
We have swords to pierce
the chests of our enemies...
...and a revenge to take for the
sake of the oppressed people!
For Allah! For the state!
For the future of Turks,
we have a long way to go!
-Your way is our way, Osman Bey!
-Thank you!
-Allah is the greatest!
Where is Halime?
Tell me where my daughter is.
Tell me where she is.
She's with Sofia.
Don't sleep. Lucia, don't sleep.
Look at me. Don't go! Look at me.
Poena.
Halime.
She's my Halime.
Doesn't she remember?
What did that snake do to my daughter?
She doesn't remember.
Sofia..
She's much worse than you think.
Tell me. How can I recognize her?
Where is Halime? Tell me.
How can I find her?
Very...
..close.
Mother! Mother!
-Son.
-Mother, a message from father.
What is it? What's going on, Boran?
My Bey says we'll take
our tribe back, Bala Hatun.
He'll wait near the tribe
for us, alps and sisters.
-Thanks to Allah. Today is the day, huh?
-Yes.
Fine. You gather alps and
sisters. We need to go. Come on.
As you order, mother.
-Let's go, Boran Bey.
-Okay.
My girl, look after her.
Watch around carefully! Stand
on alert until we find Osman!
Come on, come on!
Stand on alert until we find
Osman! Come on, come on!
Everything is for you.
Everything.
I wasn't born as a Kayi.
I became a Kayi.
I killed Ilbay for the chair.
I became Ilbay.
While I still had his blood on my hands,
...I became a father for her daughter.
I became the devil's servant for this chair.
Nobody can take this chair from me.
Nobody.
Osman has surrounded the
tribe. They're coming. Too many.
Never!
We won't let them!
Come on!
You..
...aren't my father.
You are a lying murderer.
My Bey.
Ulugan and Esenbike aren't around, my Bey.
But the vile dog called Ilbay is in the tribe.
We'll burn the bales of hay...
...and roll towards them.
With Allah's will.
...we'll take our tribe back today.
God willing, my Bey.
Osman's coming! We're under attack!
Come on, attack!
Burn.
Ya Allah... Now!
Today is the blood day!
Today is the vengeance day!
Today, we're taking back the Kayi Tribe!
Ya Allah!
No traces this way, mother.
Osman must have hidden the traces.
It's about to get dark. What now?
We can never find Osman then.
Osman has run away for now.
We're going back.
Send a message to witch Sofia.
I want her to come.
We'll make a new plan to destroy Osman.
Ilbay, you're going to die today!
They're running away, my
Bey! Going to the headquarters!
Close all the gates!
Nobody will leave here today!
Come on!
Attack!
Allah is the greatest!
You're slower, my Bey! I thought you'd have
captured the tribe by the time I arrived.
I'm slower, huh?
-Actually you still got it.
-That's what I thought!
Samil, don't let that dog run away!
As you order, my Bey.
Where are you going, jackal?
You can't go anywhere
before you pay for your betrayal.
Get up. My Bey will make you pay.
You dog. Get up, dog!
Move.
Victory is ours!
Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
-Thanks to Allah.
-Thanks to Allah, yes.
Come here.
This dog is waiting for his death now, my Bey.
What kind of a Kayi are you?
How could you betray your own kin?
Speak.
Osman Bey.
He isn't my real father, Osman Bey.
He isn't a real Kayi either.
What are you talking about, Ayse?
I heard him talking in the tent.
He killed my father and took his place.
A real Kayi would never
do what he did, Osman Bey.
My daughter...
Come, my Ayse.
Kismet!
Ayse, go.
I was very close, Osman.
I was very close to erasing you from history.
You and those like you...
...will never be able to kill me.
But...
...you and those like you...
...will die by my sword of justice.
Another traitor got what he deserved.
But the other dogs are still alive.
Ulugan has no more days to see.
But Esenbike and Sargun...
If we kill them, we will only get in trouble.
We need to capture them alive.
If we can..
We will be politically superior to Olcaytu.
What will we do now, my Bey?
Lucia.
What did you tell Bala?
Who is lying?
You..
...or...
...my aunt?
Poena..
Poena...
Forgive me...
...I am
...a horrible sinner.
Are you playing a game with me?
Did Bala threaten you?
Poena..
Sofia.
Do not trust Sofia.
You united with Bala.
You betrayed my aunt, right?
That's why my aunt wanted to kill you.
...I did...
...a very...
...bad thing...
...to you.
Meryem.
Is she awake?
No.
She is not, Gonca Hatun.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Poena..
She is saying something...
Poena.
Poena..
Forgive me...
Poena.
Halime's name.
I guess she is hallucinating
She has a high temperature.
You took our sister from us!
Even if she forgives you..
...we will not forgive you
Where is that Ilbay?
He will come here!
We punished that traitor.
We cut his head off...
You made a big mistake, Osman.
Now this war will kill you all!
Come on then.
You can all come at us!
Let's see..
Alps!
Allah is the Greatest!
Your death has come, Ulugan.
Who will save you from my hands, huh?
Attack!
You have a high temperature.
I will go and call Alaeddin Bey.
He will treat you.
...stayed silent...
..about..
...Sofia's evil plan.
I stayed..
..silent about your..
...separation from your family.
My parents are dead
You protected me.
You raised me, Lucia.
That's a lie.
Your parents are not dead.
Allah is the Greatest!
Where are you going Begum, huh?
Did you think you would get away with it?
Say your final prayer, traitor.
Say your final prayer.
Her blood is halal to me, Boran Bey.
Stop..
Handle it quickly, brother.
Come on.
Allah is the Greatest!
Now I will cut your head off.
Come at me!
Now it's time for you to die, huh?
I told you I'd take a tooth for a
tooth an eye for an eye, a life for a life!
Come at me now...
Come..
You hurt my people!
You killed my innocent people!
So, Ulugan..
Now you will die.
You are not a state, Osman.
You are just a shepherd.
The land you step on is now my land.
Here..
l am the Bey, and I am the state!
Dastard dog...
Mother, we need to leave.
Our nokers died, we cannot resist now.
When I return here, I will make sure I
don't leave a head on their shoulders!
Come on, come on mother!
Osman took his tribe back.
Esenbike and his son are running away.
Fools.
They are paying the price
for letting Osman escape.
What will we do?
Osman will be stronger than before now.
Don't let them follow us!
-Come on!
Ulugan's dog!
Altuga...
Now you will pay for all the lives you took...
...with your own life.
Your owner is a corpse now.
Now it's your turn!
Angry boys...
I should have hit that nail into
your forehead, not your hand.
I told you if you don't do it
when you have the chance...
...you'll regret it when you
are in my hands, Altuga, huh?
Altuga.
Osman Bey's door is open to everyone.
He, with Almighty Allah's order,
gives a last chance to everyone.
Now I am asking you for the last time, Altuga.
Ask for forgiveness..
...and choose The Righteous' way.
Are you serious...
Orhan?
Orhan.
Even if you cut my head off...
...I will never be your dog...
...like Cerkutay!
Never!
You, Altuga...
You chose death...
..not life.
When Cerkutay Bey hears this, he will be upset.
He was his brother in the end..
The state, Alaeddin...
The state never forgives.
Right, brother.
True.
Mother, someone's coming.
Esenbike!
I told you..
Whoever is above oneself
becomes the prey of Osman.
Now is not the day to say
meaningless words, Sofia.
Osman is after us.
-Don't worry...
I am here to save you.
Come on.
Send the horses away.
We'll go on foot.
Olcaytu will reward you for your...
...favour.
-Sure he will.
I don't do a favour without
expecting anything in return.
Mother..
Sofia.
You killed Olcaytu's daughter and grandson.
That means death!
Hristo.
I did not kill them.
Osman did.
Hristo.
How could Osman make this mistake?
Now..
Olcaytu Khan...
...will destroy...
...Kayi tribe with this furor.
Get ready.
We are leaving.
No..
My parents died.
Bala and Osman killed them.
You told me!
You told me this, I..
I lived for this!
I lived to take our revenge from them!
To kill them!
You cannot kill them.
You know the truth.
-Sofia is your executioner...
-You are lying!
My aunt was right about wanting to kill you!
You are insane!
You..
You are a traitor!
Poena..
You were her biggest, her worst...
...her most merciless game.
She raised you to make you...
...kill your own family.
You are Osman Bey...
...and Bala Hatun's...
...daughter...
...Halime.
Forgive me.
No...
What is this, my Bey?
Be careful. Bala.
Bala.
She's dead.
Who killed them? Who else was after them?
The one who tries to beat
us, while we try to bring...
...victory and hope in these lands.
He's the one who killed Esenbike.
But if don't find out who
did this with evidence...
...Olcaytu's grandson and daughter...
Their deaths will only
bring troubles to our lands.
Alps.
Take them to our tribe.
Send a messenger to Olcaytu.
Tell them to take their funerals from our tribe.
As you order, my Bey.
My brothers.
Brother.
-Thanks to Allah.
Thanks to Allah.
-Thanks to my Allah!
-Thanks to Allah.
Thanks to Allah, we took our tribe back.
Where are Bala Hatun and Osman Bey?
My Bey.
Long live Osman Bey!
Thank you, thank you.
Mother... Father.
Thank you! I appreciate it.
My Bey.
Thanks to Allah, we took our home back.
We did. Of course, we did.
Thanks to my Allah!
We believed with no doubts...
...that swords drawn for Allah...
...always become victorious!
Well..
We cleared our tribe from heathens.
With Allah's will, we became victorious!
Yet we know our target well.
Until we give our last breath
...until we bring justice
and order in the whole world
...we'll never stop!
God willing, Osman Bey!
-It's time, my Bey.
-Yes, it is.
It is time.
Praise be, Praise be. Praise be.
O the light of my state.
...rise up.
Rise up.
Stand
The tired sun is sinking
on the horizon of the west.
A new hope is rising at dawn.
Martyrs are crying out
from the intermediate realm!
You've got dragged enough!
Go up where you belong!
Rise up!
Time for the east is passing.
Here rest all the lives we sacrificed.
Dark horses are running
without you in the steppe.
The wind is always asking for you.
Rise up.
Wake up to bring order in the world.
Stand and go up with the wind.
Honorable hearts expect great news from you.
My orphan homeland demands your shadow.
Hear the cry echoing in the sky.
Mountains and rocks...
Takbir! Takbir!
They're calling you.
Wipe off the rust of your thriving pride.
Rise up.
Wave for freedom.
Stand and go up with the wind.
My plane tree shall root in your shadow.
The call of Muhammad
shall never stop in your dome!
The divine words shall
spread all around the lands.
The last Prophet is our guide.
And The Red Apple is our only path.
Stand up!
You've got dragged enough!
Carry the Turkish history on your shoulders,
and rise to the summit you are belong to!
Today is the first day of a new era.
O Allah.
In the name of Allah.